NAA Records 5775
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Mailings, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1953-1955 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  Includes correspondence about the Special Committee on membership dues plan to discuss financial affairs of the Academy at meetings which include non-members 10/53 and routine
- Schedler, Carl R., 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Hill, James C. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  Includes National War Labor Board Manual of Decisions, Preliminary and Confidential
- Hill, James C., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  Includes poems and play about the War Labor Board; War Labor Board news releases; Two decisions before Hill as Vice Chairman on the panel
- Hill, James C., 1945 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Includes War Labor Board decisions before Hill, and telegram protesting a decision
- Hill, James C., 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  Due process of arbitration notes and papers
- Hill, James C., 1960 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Hill, James C., 1961 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  Includes reports of discussions held at Regional Meeting - New York-Philadelphia chapters 9/15-7/61
- Hill, James C., 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  Includes 1962 Financial Statement
- Hill, James C., 1962 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Hill, James C., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Hill, James C. (Box 25, Folder 12)
- McKelvey, Jean T., 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- McKelvey, Jean T., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Gill, Lewis M., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Gill, Lewis M., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Gill, Lewis M., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Gill, Lewis M., 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Treasures Reports, 1950-1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  scattered issues
- Treasures Reports, 1950-1977 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Treasures Reports, 1950-1977 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Financial Records, Reports and Correspondence, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Financial Records, Reports and Correspondence, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Financial Records, Reports and Correspondence, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Financial Records, Reports and Correspondence, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Receipts and Expenditures, 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Financial Affairs Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Treasurers Files IRS, 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Treasurers Files IRS, 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Receipts and Expenditures, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Executive Committee, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  Includes Minutes of Executive Committee meeting 11/1/54 which report Nominating Committee decisions, relations with American Arbitration Association; correspondence about arbitration statutes and routine
- Executive Committee, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  Includes Minutes of Executive Committee meeting 3/29/58 which discusses improving liaison with American Arbitration Association, the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, and other appointing agencies
- Executive Committee, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  Summary of meeting between NAA, American Arbitration Association and Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service 6/12/62. 10p. and routine
- Executive Committee, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  Includes correspondence about excessive fees in arbitration, plans for training program; "Creation and Conduct of Program For Training of Labor Arbitrators "n.d., 2p.
- Executive Committee, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  Includes Report of Special Committee on Incorporation 10/64. 2p.; correspondence from Frederic Anderson regarding excessive arbitrators fees 2/64, 6p.
- Executive Committee, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  Correspondence regarding the Academy's paying one-half of the expenses incurred in the Cleveland training program; correspondence about asking Cy Ching to join NAA; regarding statement of affirmation required of members; "Tentative proposal seeking support for a Comprehensible Research Program in Arbitration and establishment of Continuing Study Committees, both under the auspices of the National Academy of Arbitrators" Working draft, 8/6/65,12p.
- Executive Committee, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Executive Committee, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Executive Committee, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  Includes report by the Committee on Ethics and Grievances, 5p.
- Executive Committee, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Executive Committee, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  "Policies of the National Academy of Arbitrators as Evidenced by Minutes of Annual Meetings and Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Governors "n.d., 6p. and routine correspondence
- Executive Committee, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  Correspondence about statutes of the Academy with the Internal Revenue Service
- Executive Committee, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  Includes correspondence about including Steven Kane's paper on Bench Decisions in the Proceedings of the twenty-fifth annual meeting and routine correspondence
- Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  Correspondence regarding whether or not to re-process the application of resigned member Thomas Knowlton; correspondence about how to honor Abe Stockman and routine
- Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  Correspondence about proposed amendments to the constitution and Bylaws, about the proposed AAA "Wingspread Conference"; proposed "Code of Professional Responsibility" and related correspondence; correspondence about Department of Labor proposal to evaluate several NAA arbitrator training programs
- Executive Committee, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Executive Committee, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Executive Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  Correspondence regarding memorializing Leo Brown and David Cole
- Executive Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  Handwritten notes
- Board of Governors, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Board of Governors, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  Minutes
- Board of Governors, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Board of Governors, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  Misc.
- Board of Governors, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Board of Governors, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Board of Governors, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Board of Governors, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  Minutes; Includes discussion of "Membership Policy"; "Statement of Academy Purposes and Aims"; a description of the "Education and Research Committee."
- Board of Governors, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Board of Governors, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Board of Governors, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  Subcommittee on Education and Training - Interim Report
- Board of Governors, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Board of Governors, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  Correspondence; Includes Correspondence relating to the Babylon Milk and Cream Co., Inc. V. Horvitz, et al, and the issue of "the civil liability of an arbitrator in the exercise of his functions
- Board of Governors, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  Legislative Committee
- Board of Governors, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  Reports and Resolutions; contains resolution opposing the enactment of the Uniform Arbitration Act.
- Board of Governors, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  Financial Records
- Board of Governors, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  Misc.; Includes remarks by Joseph F. Finnegan (Director, Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service) on the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, 6p.
- Board of Governors, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Board of Governors, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  Correspondence; Includes Abram Stockman reports Aaron Horvitz's Lawyer advises against the submission of a brief amicus curiae; "Report to the Board of Governors by the Vice President in Charge of Regional Activities, 7p.
- Board of Governors, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  Reports and Resolutions; Contains report and recommendations from the Special Committee to consider the Aims and Purposes of the Academy, 4p.
- Board of Governors, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Board of Governors, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Board of Governors, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Board of Governors, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Board of Governors, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  Correspondence; Includes discussion of "Publication of Cases"; Proposed revision of the constitution and Bylaws. 6p.; Third draft of the United States Labor Arbitration Act, 21p.
- Board of Governors, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Board of Governors, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Board of Governors, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  Committees (various)
- Board of Governors, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  Reports and Resolutions
- Board of Governors, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Board of Governors, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  Misc.; Includes a list of National Academy of Arbitrators officers and Board of Governors, as well as a list of delinquent members
- Board of Governors, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  Minutes; Includes discussion of the findings of the Committee on Structure; recommended dues increase
- Board of Governors, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Board of Governors, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  Correspondence; Includes "Summary of Chicago Group's Reaction to the Seward Project"; questions relating to the investigation of an arbitrator by the Department of Labor
- Board of Governors, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Board of Governors, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  Correspondence; Regarding the status of arbitrators and the income tax; arbitration costs; "associate member" status
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  Reports and Resolutions; Includes study on the cost of arbitration
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Board of Governors, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  Misc.; Includes "Policies of the National Academy of arbitrators as Evidenced by Minutes of Annual Meetings and minutes of the Board of Governors"
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  Academy Policies Study - Correspondence and Report; Includes "Policies of the National Academy of Arbitrators as Evidenced by Minutes of Annual Meetings and Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Governors." 6p.
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  Defense Fund Correspondence; Correspondence pertaining to a lawsuit involving G Allan Dash Jr.; the Rationality Blouses case
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  Special Committee on Membership Status - Correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  Special Committee on Membership Status - Background Material
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  Special Committee on Ethical Conduct and Grievance Committee Questionnaire
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  Special Committee on Grievance Machinery - Correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  Special Committee on Grievance Machinery - Constitution and Bylaws, Amendment
- Board of Governors, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 58)
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 59)
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 60)
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  Correspondence; Concerning a "bibliography of member publications; establishing a Kentucky-Indiana- Ohio Region; Guest Invitation policy; the Liaison, 5p.
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 62)
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 63)
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 64)
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 65)
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  Special Committee on Membership Status Correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  Committee on Grievance Machinery - Correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  Committee on Grievance Machinery - memos and minutes; Includes "Enforcing the Ethical Code", 14p.
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  Special Committee on Training of New Arbitrators
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 70)
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  Reports and Resolutions; Includes "Report by the Chairman of the Liaison Committee"
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 72)
- Board of Governors, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 73)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  Correspondence; Relating to jurisdictional conflicts between NAA and the National Labor Relations Board; Report of the Special Committee on Grievance Machinery, with attached "Proposed Amendments to the Constitution and Bylaws"; "The Advisability of Incorporation"
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  Academy Policies Study
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  Committee on Grievance Machinery - Minutes
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  Committee on Grievance Machinery Correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  Committee on Grievance Machinery Reports
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  Committee on Grievance Machinery - Reports
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  Committee on the Training of New Arbitrators - Correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  Committee on the Training of New Arbitrators - Reports
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  Committee on Ethics and Grievances - Correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  Committee on Development and Long Range Goals
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  Special Committee on Incorporation
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Board of Governors, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  Correspondence; Regarding the "admission of Cy Ching to membership"; "proposal to Establish as a continuing institution on "arbitration conference" as an adjunct of the National Academy of Arbitrators" 7p.; the Ethics Committee
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  Special Committee on Training of New Arbitrators - Minutes, Correspondence, Reports
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  Committee on Ethics and Grievance - Minutes, Correspondence, Reports
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  Special Committee on Development and Long Range Goals - Misc.
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  Arrangements Committee - Reports
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Board of Governors, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  Correspondence; Includes Lawrence E. Seibel's discussion of membership policy.3p.; questions being "explored" by the Committee on Ethics and Grievances, 5p.; "The Seinsheimer Application for NAA membership."
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  Special Committee on Membership Status - Correspondence and Statement
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  Special Committee on Training of New Arbitrators - Minutes, correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  Committee on Ethics and Grievances Minutes
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  Committee on Ethics and Grievances Correspondence; Includes "questions to be considered ...", 7p.; A. Langley Coffey's discussion of an Academy member functioning as "a partisan member of tripartite board of arbitration', 3p.; Sylvester Garrett's analysis of the Seinsheimer case; an :advisory opinion: on infighting guests to the Annual Meeting from Sylvester Garrett.
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  Special Committee on Development and Long Range Goals - Minutes, correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Board of Governors, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  Miscellaneous
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  Correspondence; Includes discussion of the "dues structure"; reimbursement for travel expenses; retirement/pension plan - specifically "Explanation of Keough Act (9 pp), attached to letter from Bert L. Luskin
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 56)
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 57)
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 58)
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 59)
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  Special Committee on Training of New Arbitrator, - minutes, correspondence
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  Committee on Ethnics and Grievances - minutes, correspondence, report
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  Membership Committee - report
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  Report on Pension Plan
- Board of Governors, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 64)
- Board of Governors, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  Minutes; Includes discussion of Academy finances; essay contest, corresponding members
- Board of Governors, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 66)
- Board of Governors, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 67)
- Board of Governors, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 68)
- Board of Governors, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 69)
  Reports; Report of the Committee on Cooperation with the National Labor Relations Board
- Board of Governors, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 70)
- Board of Governors, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Board of Governors, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 72)
  Correspondence; Includes Annual Report of the Secretary; financial records
- Board of Governors, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 73)
  Committee on Grievance Machinery - Report
- Board of Governors, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 74)
  Material on the Relationship with Overseas Neutrals - Includes "Report on Proposed NAA Relationship with Overseas Neutrals" (3 pp)
- Board of Governors, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 75)
  Reports and Resolutions; Includes "Resolution on Billing for Cancellations and Postponements"
- Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Minutes; Includes discussion of Guest List Policy; Annual Volume of Proceedings; Legal Affairs Committee
- Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  Correspondence; Includes "Master Guest List for Invitations to the Annual Meeting" (71 pp.); preview of publication "Reflections of an Arbitrator"
- Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  Committee on Essay Contest
- Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  Special Committee on Guest Policy
- Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  Special Committee for Standards for Membership
- Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  Reports and Resolutions; Includes report on "Qualifying the Academy for Tax Exemption Under the Internal Revenue Code"
- Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  Miscellaneous; Includes "Survey of the Arbitration Profession"
- Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  Minutes; Includes discussion of dues; "The Development of New Arbitrators" (18 pp)
- Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  Correspondence; Includes discussion "Report of Special Committee on
- Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  Reports and Resolutions; Includes the Annual Report of the Secretary
- Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Board of Governors, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  Minutes; Includes correspondence relating to Ethnics and Grievances
- Board of Governors, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Board of Governors, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Board of Governors, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Board of Governors, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Board of Governors, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  Correspondence; Includes "Proposed New Section 6 to Article VI of the
- Board of Governors, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  Committee on Development of New Arbitration - Correspondence Miscellaneous; Includes reports; bibliography of graduates from NCLA -Institute of Industrial Relations; survey of arbitrator
- Board of Governors, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Board of Governors, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Board of Governors, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  Minutes; Includes "Presentation and Discussion of Proposed Code"
- Board of Governors, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Board of Governors, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  Correspondence; Contains "Code of Professional Responsibility" (22 pp)
- Board of Governors, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Board of Governors, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  Committee on Development - Includes discussion of the expedited arbitration program; National Neutral Training Program (16 pp)
- Board of Governors, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Board of Governors, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  Reports and Resolution; Includes "Evaluations of Programs Seeking to Develop Arbitrator Acceptability" (25 pp)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  Minutes; Includes "Proposed Resolution and Change" (4 pp); Discussion of the history of the Academy; Committee on the Academy; Committee on the Development of New Arbitrators; Reexamination Committee; Revised Report of the Committee on Academy Dues and Expenditures (30 pp)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 37)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Correspondence; Includes discussion of the "Nomination to Academy Offices", Amendments to the Constitution and By-Laws (22 pp)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  Committee on Development of New Arbitrators Includes surveys of "Persons Admitted to NAA Since 1970"
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  Committee on Development of New Arbitrators Includes surveys of "Persons Admitted to NAA Since 1970".
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  Special Committee to Review Membership and Related Policy Questions of the Academy
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Board of Governors, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Board of Governors, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 10)